Enola Gay Exhibition Records, 1993-1999
Smithsonian Institution Archives
Enola Gay Exhibition Records
1993-1999
Smithsonian Institution Archives, Washington, D.C., osiaref@si.edu
National Air and Space Museum
SI Records
1 cu. ft. (1 record storage box)
Accession 08-072
Descriptive Entry
This accession consists of records maintained by Joanne M. Gernstein London, Curator, documenting the planning and design of exhibitions and events related to the Enola Gay. Materials include correspondence, memoranda, draft scripts, notes, images, clippings, floor plans, an audiotape, a poster, and related materials.
Index Terms
This collection is indexed under the following access terms. These are links to collections with related topics, persons or places.
Name
London, Joanne M. Gernstein, 1961-; Enola Gay (Bomber)
Subject
Exhibitions; Aeronautical museums
Physical Characteristics of Materials in the Collection
Clippings; Manuscripts; Floor plans; Posters; Black-and-white negatives; Black-and-white transparencies; Color photographs; Color transparencies; Audiotapes
- Box 1
  - Enola Gay Exhibition - Draft Scripts, December 1993-January 1994 (4 folders) (Box 1 of 1)
  - Enola Gay Exhibition - 509th Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 1 of 1)
  - Enola Gay Exhibition - Fred Bock, 1995 (Box 1 of 1)
  - Enola Gay - Miscellaneous 509th Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 1 of 1)
  - The Last Act - Notes and Miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 1 of 1)
  - The Last Act - Objects and Images (Box 1 of 1)
  - Enola Gay Exhibition - Correspondence, 1993-1997 (Box 1 of 1)
  - Enola Gay - Reunion, 1997-1999 (Box 1 of 1)
  - Hiroshima/Pearl Harbor Poster (Box 1 of 1)
  - Enola Gay Exhibition - Articles and Thoughts, 1993 (Box 1 of 1)
  - Enola Gay Exhibition - Notes on Criticisms (Box 1 of 1)
  - Enola Gay Exhibition and Films, 1993-1995 (Box 1 of 1)
  - Enola Gay Exhibition and the 509th - Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 1 of 1)
  - 509th Composite Group, 1993-1997 (Box 1 of 1)
  - 509th Reunion - Correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box 1 of 1)
  - 509th Reunion - Chicago (Box 1 of 1)
  - Enola Gay Exhibition - CH7 (Psychology of A-Bombers and Survivors of Hiroshima) (Box 1 of 1)
  - 509th Reunion, 1994 (Box 1 of 1)
  - Enola Gay Films (Box 1 of 1)
  - Enola Gay - Castle Exhibition, 1995 (Box 1 of 1)
  - George Hicks, 1994 (Box 1 of 1)
  - 509th Composite Group, 1993 (Box 1 of 1)
  - Enola Gay Slides, 1995 (Box 1 of 1)